Preliminary Guide to the Marine Laboratory Records, 1931-2006 UA.18.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession Number A88-0055
  - Subject Files
    - Costs for PL-480 expenditures: training of foreign scientists (Box 9)
    - Courtesy Associates Escort Service, etc. in Washington D.C. (Box 9)
    - Cowles, Tim, Zoology - working with Barber (Box 10)
    - Cowles, Mr. Tim (Box 10)
    - Cox, Dr. James (Box 10)
    - Cronin, Mr. Thomas (Box 10)
    - Cronin, Tom - Zoology - Forward (Box 10)
    - Cruz, Gustavo (Honduras), ITPMS Participant, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Currents (Box 10)
    - Cutler, Dr. Edward (Box 10)
    - Cuzin-Roudy, Janine (France) (Box 10)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Da Silva, Eduardo, Brazil (ITPMS 1978 Participants) (Box 10)
    - Davies (Box 10)
    - De Cleir, Dr. Walter, Director, University of Antwerp, Belgium (Box 10)
    - de Langlande, Dr. Ron, Wittenberg University (Box 10)
    - de Mendiola, Mrs. Blanca Rojas (1977 ITPMS participant) (Box 10)
    - de Pauw, Neils (Box 10)
    - de Silva, Sena (ITPMS 1978 participant) (Box 10)
    - Department of State - AID (Agency for International Development) (Box 10)
    - Derby, Charles (Box 10)
    - Dietrich, Donna (Box 10)
    - Dillaman, Dr. Richard, Duke Zoology Dept. (Box 10)
    - Dimock, Dr. Ronald (Box 10)
    - Diving (Box 10)
    - Diving Operations, memo from John Sutherland, October 27, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Djangmah, Dr. J.S., University of Cape Coast, Ghana (Box 10)
    - Driver's License (Box 10)
    - Duarte, William (1977 ITPMS participant) (Box 10)
    - Dunlap, Mrs. Connie (Box 10)
    - Dybern, Dr. Brent I. (the Phillippines) (Box 10)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Ebert, Mr. Harry (Box 10)
    - Edding, Prof. Mario (1977 ITMPS participant) (Box 10)
    - Edwards, Ms. Judy Clarke (Box 10)
    - Edwards, Dr. Robert L., NOAA, Woods Hole (Box 10)
    - Eger, William H., Dept. of Marine Science, U. Puerto Rico, Mayaguez, P.R. (Box 10)
    - Eglund, Ms. A.M., Uppsala, Sweden (Box 10)
    - El-Gameey, Nagati Younes (Egypt), participant ETP, 1978 (Box 10)
    - El Haq, Abu Gabr, Sudan (Box 10)
    - Ellington, Ross (Box 10)
    - Elsevier - North Holland Publishing, Amsterdam, the Netherlands (Box 10)
    - Duke Endowment Conference (Box 10)
    - Epoch (Box 10)
    - Escofet, Anamaria (Argentina), ITPMS 1978 Participant (Box 10)
    - Proposed Scheduling of Events for Fall 1979 (Box 10)
    - Exxon (Box 10)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Minutes (on campus) (Box 10)
    - Fagetti, Dr. Elda (Box 10)
    - Martha C. Farmer - Physiology, Graduate Student 1975 (working in biochemistry) (Box 10)
    - Films (Box 10)
    - Fisher, Tom (Box 10)
    - Thomas Fisher - Curriculum Vita (Box 10)
    - Fisher, Dr. Thomas (Box 10)
    - Tom Fisher - MS, "Cost of Metabolic Maintenance" (Box 10)
    - Tom Fisher - NSF Grant (Box 10)
    - Fisher and Barber NSF, March 1976-February 1978 (Box 10)
    - Fisheries Bulletin MS Review - Euphausia pacifica by D.R. Craddock, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Florida Board of Rights - State University System of Florida, 1977 (Box 10)
    - State of Florida, Dept. of Environment Regulation Review, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Florida State University (Box 10)
    - Foreign Visitors (Box 10)
    - Franssen, Mr. H.P. (Box 10)
    - Fritz, Robert E., Durham (Box 10)
    - Furman University (Box 10)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Gaill, Mlle. Francoise (France) (Box 10)
    - Galler, Dr. Sid (Box 10)
    - Gallucci, Vincent (Box 10)
    - General and Comparative Endocrinology Journal (Box 10)
    - Gianazza, Elisabetta, Milano, Italy, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Giere, Olav (Germany) (Box 10)
    - Gilchrist, Mrs. John (Box 10)
    - Gilles, Drs. Michelle and Raymond (Belgium) (Box 10)
    - Glaeser, Dr. J. Douglas (Box 10)
    - Glaeser
      - Sedimentary Models as Exploration Guides (Box 10)
      - Comparisons of Long and Short Term Changes in a Barrier Island... (Box 10)
      - Proposal to Dr. Rachlin (Box 10)
      - Proposal with Dennis Weiss (Box 10)
      - Preliminary Proposal--Hudson River Estuary (Box 10)
    - Gleeson, Dr. Richard A. - VIMS (Box 10)
    - Glemarec, Prof. M., Lab of Biological Oceanography - Brest, France (Box 10)
    - Godfrey, Dr. Paul (Box 10)
    - Goll, Robert, Review of three-year term, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Goll, Dr. Robert M. (Box 10)
    - Goll, NSF
      - Origins and Early Evolution of Colosphaerid Radiolaria, 1979 (Box 10)
      - Late Pleistocene preservation of radio larian, 1978 (Box 10)
      - Lithologica and biostratigraph analysis of DSDP, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Gooch, Dr. James (Box 10)
    - Gordon and Breach, Publishers (Box 10)
    - Gosling, Dr. Elizabeth, University College, Galway, Ireland (Box 10)
    - Goudeau, Dr. Marie, Laboratoire de Zoologie, Faculte des Sciences de Paris, France (Box 10)
    - Graduate Faculty Executive Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - Graduate School - General (Box 10)
    - Graduate School - Round Table on Science and Public Affairs Lecture (Box 10)
    - Graduate Students
      - 1966 (Box 10)
      - 1967 (Box 10)
      - Duke University, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Current Zoology Dept., 1976 (Box 11)
      - 1978 (Box 11)
      - Department of Zoology Fall 1969 (Box 11)
      - Inquiries 1975-1976, [2 folders] (Box 11)
      - Summer/Fall Registration, 1977 (Box 11)
      - Training Programs to pay tuition (Box 11)
      - Graduate Student Weekend
        - 1971 (Box 11)
        - 1974 (Box 11)
        - 1975 (Box 11)
        - 1977 (Box 11)
      - Zoology Department 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - Registration Changes, Spring 1977 (Box 11)
    - Grassle, Judy and Fred (Box 11)
    - Graves, Jim (Box 11)
    - Gross, Dr. Paul (Box 11)
    - Grossfield, NC State University Physiologist (Robert) (Box 11)
    - Gulka, Gary J. - Lafayette (Box 11)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Hadfield, Dr. Michael G., Pac Biomed Res Ctr, Univ. Hawaii (Box 11)
    - Haefner, Dr. Paul A., Jr., Rochester Inst Technology (Box 11)
    - Haines, Evelyn Brown (Box 11)
    - Halim, Y. (Box 11)
    - Halbrecht, Mr. H., Stamford, CT (Box 11)
    - Hall, Mrs. Reba (Box 11)
    - Hamali, Nuri El (Libya (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Dr. Heyward - DOE, Washington (Box 11)
    - Hammond, Dr. Robert D. (Box 11)
    - Handler, Dr. Philip (Box 11)
    - Haq, S.M. (Box 11)
    - Harame, Mr. David (Box 11)
    - Harbor Branch Foundation (Box 11)
    - Harris, Dr. J.E. (Australia (Box 11)
    - Hastings, Dr. David (Box 11)
    - Hayward, Dr. Thomas L. (Box 11)
    - Hebrank, Mary (Reidy) (Box 11)
    - Hedgpeth, Joel (Box 11)
    - Herrick, Allan M., DU Development Office (Box 11)
    - Herring, Sally (Box 11)
    - Hester, Frances (Spring 77 Student) (Box 11)
    - Hill, Ms. Janet (Box 11)
    - Hodges, Undersecretary Luther, Dept of Commerce, Washington DC (Box 11)
    - Hoffmann, Rolf - grad student, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Holt, Mr. Deane - IDOE, NSF (Box 11)
    - Hopkins, Dr. Tom S., Brookhaven National Lab, Upton, NY (Box 11)
    - Horn, Mrs. Edith W. (Box 11)
    - Horne, Mr. Craig (Box 11)
    - Howard, Mr. Ken (Box 11)
    - Howe, Duncan - Zoology (Box 11)
    - Hughes, Prof. George, Univ. Bristol, England (Box 11)
    - Humphries, Edythe (Box 11)
    - Hunt, Dr. Linda-Margaret, University of Notre Dame (Box 11)
    - Huntsman, Dr. Susan (Box 11)
    - Hutchinson, Judith, Grad Student, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Hyatt, Gary (Box 11)
    - Ibrahim, Ezzat Awwad (Box 11)
    - Independent Study (Box 11)
    - US Information Agency (Box 11)
    - Infrared Aerial Photos (Box 11)
    - Inquireies (Miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - International Development Research Center (Box 11)
    - International House (Durham) (Box 11)
    - International Training (Box 11)
    - International Training Program, Planning for future (after 1979) (Box 11)
    - International Visitors, 1975-1979 (Box 11)
    - Invitations (Box 11)
    - ITPMS for Maniculture (Box 11)
    - ITPMS Letter to Alumni, July 1979 (Box 11)
    - ITPMS - Letters Re. Funding sources for future, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Iturriaga, Rodolfo, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Jackson, Mr. Richard (Box 11)
    - US-Japan Cooperative Science Program (Box 11)
    - Japanese Marine Biology Research Institutes List (Box 11)
    - Jenner, Charles - Dept of Zoology, UNC Chapel Hill (Box 11)
    - Jensen, Ms. Margit (Box 11)
    - Joerg, Dean Frederick (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Mr. Charles (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Mr. David (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Lucinda (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Dr. T.W., Jr. (Box 11)
    - Joyner, Mr. Ron (Box 11)
    - Julliard, Francine (Box 11)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Kane, Mr. Thomas E. (Box 11)
    - Kannupandi, Dr. T. - India (1977 ITPMS participant) (Box 11)
    - Karlson, Dr. Ron (Box 11)
    - Karlson, Ron - Zoology (Box 11)
    - Kassem, Hamid Hmeda, Univ. Garyounis, Benghazi, Libya (Box 11)
    - Kazmi, Afzal - Pakistan (1978 ITPMS participant) (Box 11)
    - Kaufman, Wally, Heartwood Realty, Carrboro, NC (Box 11)
    - Kelleher, Michael J., 1977 Spring term (Box 11)
    - Kellogg, Dr. Charles (Box 11)
    - Khalaf, Dr. A. N., Biological Res. Ctr., Baghdad, Iraq (Box 11)
    - Khan, Ms. Badr-un-nisa (Pakistan) (Box 11)
    - King, Doris (Box 11)
    - King, Mr. Lauriston R. (Lorry), NSF, Washington, DC (Box 11)
    - King, Tanya (Hastler) (Box 11)
    - Knauss, Dr. John (Box 11)
    - Kohl, Dr. Jerome (Box 11)
    - Koltun (USSR) (Box 11)
    - Koulish, Dr. Sasha (Box 11)
    - Kreps, Juanita (Secretary of Commerce) (Box 11)
    - Krigbaum, Dr. William R. (Box 11)
    - Kropach, Dr. Chaim - Israel Oceanogr Limnol Research, Haifa, Israel (Box 11)
    - Kuris, A.M. (Box 11)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Laboratories (East Coast) (Box 12)
    - Lamont-Doherty, Palisades, NY - Current Publications, November 1976 (Box 12)
    - Lamy, Jean, Univ. of Tours, France (Box 12)
    - Landau, Matthew (Box 12)
    - Lane, Sandra E. (Sandy), Kenyon College (Box 12)
    - Lang, Dr. Michael A. (Box 12)
    - Lapannas, Dr. George (Box 12)
    - Lassene, Dr. Pierre (France) (Box 12)
    - Latz, Mr. Michael (Box 12)
    - Law, School of (Box 12)
    - Lehigh University (Center for Marine and Environmental Studies) (Box 12)
    - Leigh, Ian J. (1977 ITMPS participant (Box 12)
    - Leuenberger, Andreas, Panama (Box 12)
    - Leversee, Dr. Gordon (Box 12)
    - Lewis, Dean Harold (Box 12)
    - Lilly Scholars Visit to DUML, April 14, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Lilly Sciences Seminar, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Limburg, Mr. Peter R. (Box 12)
    - Link, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Link Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - Link Foundation, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Linton, Dr. Thomas (Box 12)
    - Litaker, Wayne (Box 12)
    - Litton, Ms. Laura (Box 12)
    - Livingston, Dr. Robert J., Florida STate Univ., Tallahassee (Box 12)
    - Longstreth, Dr. David J. (Box 12)
    - Lucas, John (Australia) (Box 12)
    - Lucas, J.S. (Box 12)
    - Lundalv, Tomas (Sweden) (Box 12)
    - Lundberg, Dr. John (Box 12)
    - Lunz, John David, Corps of Engineers, Vicksburg, MS (Box 12)
    - Luzzi, Lynn Ann (Box 12)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Macaranas, Julie - Philippines (ITPMS 1978 participant) (Box 12)
    - MacDonald, Dr. Eve (Box 12)
    - Mane, Mr. Uday H., Odessa, USSR (Box 12)
    - Marine Environmental Research: London, England and Sequim Washington (new journal 1979) (Box 12)
    - Martens, Christopher (Box 12)
    - Martin, Joe, Biochemistry Dept, Graduate Student, 1975 (Box 12)
    - University of Maryland, Sea Grant Program (Box 12)
    - Matsuda, Dr. R. (Box 12)
    - Maxwell, Dr. Sandra E., New Bern (Box 12)
    - McCarthy, John F., Union Carbide, Oak Ridge (Box 12)
    - McCarthy, Dr. M.F. (Ireland) (Box 12)
    - McCloskey, Dr. Lawrence (Box 12)
    - McCrimmon, Dr. Donald A. (Box 12)
    - McDermott, Dr. John (Box 12)
    - McKinney, Dean John (Box 12)
    - Menge, Dr. Jane Lubchenco (Box 12)
    - Metalnikov, Dr. A.P., Moscow, USSR (Box 12)
    - Michel, Harding B. (Box 12)
    - Mid-Pacific Marine Laboratory Workshop - rescheduled February 8-9, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Mikhail, Mr. Nabil Y., Los Angeles, CA (from Egypt) (Box 12)
    - Miller, Jennifer - Chapel Hill (Box 12)
    - Mitchell, Dr. Kenneth (U.K.) (Box 12)
    - Mohan, Dr. R.S. Lal (India) (Box 12)
    - Mohsen, Dr. Lotfi, Embassy of Egypt, Washington, DC (Box 12)
    - Mokhtarzad, Shahnaz - Iran (ITPMS 1978 participant) (Box 12)
    - [Monitor], 1975-1982, [Folders 1-4 of 6], [4 folders] (Box 12)
    - [Monitor], 1975-1982, [Folders 5-6 of 6], [2 folders] (Box 13)
    - Monitor, [2 folders] (Box 13)
    - The Monitor - Filming by Calypso and Jacques Cousteau - visit to DUML (Box 13)
    - Monitor Marine Sanctuary, Technical Review Committee meeting, Raleigh, February 16, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Monitor Meeting, Raleigh, March 5, 1979-March 6, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Monitor, Nat'l Conference, Raleigh, April 2, 1978-April 4, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Monitor Tech Adv. Comm/Govt Rev. Comm. Meeting, Raleigh, April 29, 1980-April 30, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Moorefield, Mr. Bruce L. (Box 13)
    - Journal of Morphology (Box 13)
    - Morrill, Dr. John B., Univ. S. Florida (Box 13)
    - Murillo, Dr. Manuel M., San Jose, Costa Rica (Box 13)
    - N Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Nagamine, Mr. Claude (Box 13)
    - Nascimento, Iracema - Bahia, Brazil (Box 13)
    - Natarajan, Dr. R. (Box 13)
    - National Aeronautics and Space - NASA Post-IDOE Information - Space Systems/remote sensing (Box 13)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 13)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 13)
    - National Council on Marine Resources and Engineering Development (Box 13)
    - National Institutes of Health: Bonaventura proposal (Box 13)
    - Nawar, Dr. G. - Cairo, Egypt (Box 13)
    - NCSU "Energy from the Oceans - Fact or Fantasy" - cancelled, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Nelson, Mary Ann - general staff artist, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Nelson, Walt - zoology (Box 13)
    - Nelson, Walter G. (grad student 1977) (Box 13)
    - Visit by News Service and reporters, June 7, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Nidek, Dr. Don (Box 13)
    - Biomaterials - NIH, BRAC (Biomaterials Research Advisory Committee), 1969 (Box 13)
    - Nijhout, Dr. Frederick (Box 13)
    - North Carolina State University (Box 13)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Ocean (Box 13)
    - Oceanographic Institution Mailing to Trustees, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Oceanographic Program, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
    - Coastal Upwelling Ecosystems Analysis - Oceanography (Box 13)
    - Oceanography - Ship Scheduling Committee, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Oceanography, UNOLS, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Odum, Dr. H.T., Gainesville, FL (Box 13)
    - Olive, Dr. P.J.W. - Dove Marine Lab, Cullercoats Bay, North Shields, England (Box 13)
    - Omori, Dr. M. - UNESCO, Div. Sciences (Box 13)
    - Oregon Site Visit, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Oregon State University - Dedication of Instructional Wing - Keynote address by JDC, March 17, 1978 (Box 13)
    - University of Oregon (Box 13)
    - Organization for Tropical Studes (OTS) (Box 13)
    - Organization of American States (OAS) (Box 13)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Marine Seminar, Palm Beach, FL (Box 13)
    - Pandian, Dr. T.J. - Madurai Kamaraj Univ., Madurai, India (Box 13)
    - Emilia Pandolfelli Ph.D. - Bronx, NY, postdoc with biochemistry (Box 13)
    - Park Central Hotel - Washington, DC (Box 13)
    - Parsley, Patricia E. (grad student, Botany) (Box 13)
    - Pebrye, Celine (France) (Box 13)
    - Pechenik et al. manuscript review, March 1978 (Box 13)
    - Pergamon Press Ltd - Oxford, England (Box 13)
    - Petrie, Lloyd, Chemistry (Box 13)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Group Meeting - France (Box 13)
    - Phillips, Bruce (Australia) (Box 13)
    - Pierson, Dr. Bernice - Bethesda, Maryland (Box 13)
    - Postdoctoral Positions Available (Box 13)
    - Postdoc Inquiries (Box 13)
    - Polo, Dr. Francisco Pineda (Box 13)
    - Prakash, Dr. A. - EPS, Ontario, Can. (Box 13)
    - Predoctoral Research Service Awards Program - NIH (Box 13)
    - Pressure Experiment (Box 13)
    - Price, Dr. Christopher (Box 13)
    - Proposal by Whitney Godwin and Nan Sterman - May 1, 1979-August 31, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Proposal for Symposium on Cooperative Programs in Developing Nations, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Proposal (Hunter Sharp), 1980 (Box 13)
    - Prusch, Dr. Robert (Box 13)
    - Q Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Qasim, Dr. S.Z. - Goa, India (Box 13)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - Rahn, Dr. Hermann - SUNY, Buffalo, NY (Box 14)
    - Rechnitzer, Dr. A.B. (Box 14)
    - Recommendations (Box 14)
    - Recommendations, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Recommendations - to be written (Box 14)
    - Reed, Ms. Martha (Box 14)
    - Regnault, Ms. Michele (France) (Box 14)
    - Reish, Dr. Donald (Box 14)
    - Rental possibilities for lab in Beaufort (Box 14)
    - Research, Summer 1976 (Box 14)
    - Research Inquiries (Box 14)
    - Research Space, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
    - Rex, Dr. Michael A. (Box 14)
    - Rhodes, Mr. Raymond J. - SC Wildlife/Marine Res. Dept. (Box 14)
    - Richardson, Dr. Ralph William Jr. (Box 14)
    - Richmond, Dr. Addison - US Embassy, Cairo, Egypt (Box 14)
    - Riedl, Prof. Rupert - Institute of Biology, Vienna, Austria (Box 14)
    - Righetti, Drs. Piergiorgio and Adriana, Milano, Italy (Box 14)
    - Roberts, John L. (Box 14)
    - Robertson, Prof. Horace B., Jr. - Professor of Law, Duke, Durham (Box 14)
    - Robertson, Dr. J. David - Dept. Anatomy, DU (Box 14)
    - Roer, Mr. Robert (Box 14)
    - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Russell-Hunter, Dr. W.D. - Editor, Biological Bulletin (Box 14)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - Said, Mahmoud Mohamed (Egypt) (Box 14)
    - Salvat, Mariana - Argentina (ITPMS 1978 Participant) (Box 14)
    - Sastry, Dr. A.N. (Box 14)
    - Sastry, Dr. A.N. (documents) (Box 14)
    - Savage, Prof. Godfrey H. (Box 14)
    - Sawyer, Mr. Robert N. (Box 14)
    - Scheltema, Dr. Rudolph (Box 14)
    - Scheltema, Rudolf S. (documents) (Box 14)
    - Schloss, Jeffrey Allen (spring and fall 1978) (Box 14)
    - Schmertz, Kennedy B. - Smithsonian Foreign Currency (Box 14)
    - Schmidt-Nielsen, Dr. Knut (Box 14)
    - Schmiede, Pablo (Chile (Box 14)
    - Schneider, David, 1967 Thesis (Box 14)
    - Sastry, Dr. A.N. (Box 14)
    - Schoffeniels, Dr. Ernest (Belgium) (Box 14)
    - Schwantes, Arno R. (Box 14)
    - Schwartz, Dr. Frank (Box 14)
    - Schwarz, Dr. Robert - Eastern Medical Surgical Supply (Box 14)
    - Science Bulletin (Box 14)
    - Seas - "Title, Uses of the Seas" (Box 14)
    - Seaver, Mr. Don (Box 14)
    - Sellers, Ms. Susan C. (former student) (Box 14)
    - Shannon, Dr. Wayne - Univ. Connecticut, STORRS (Box 14)
    - Sharp, Ms. Jane - Raleigh, NC (Box 14)
    - Shulenberger, Dr. Eric (Box 14)
    - Siddall, Dr. John B. - Zoecon Corp., Palo Alto, CA (Box 14)
    - Sierra Club (Box 14)
    - Siudzinski, Kazimierz (Box 14)
    - Smith, Guy Roy (John de Wolf) (Box 14)
    - Smith, Dr. Sharon (Box 14)
    - Smith, Dr. Walker (Box 14)
    - Smith, Walker - Zoology (Box 14)
    - Smisth, Ms. Wendy (Box 14)
    - Southern Living Magazine - visit May 16-18, 1979 to do photos/story (Box 14)
    - SREB - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 14)
    - Staff and Students at DUML, November 1967 (Box 14)
    - Stewart, Dr. M. - Open Univ., Bucks, UK (Box 14)
    - Stotz, Wolfgang - Chile (ITPMS 1978 Participant) (Box 14)
    - Struhsaker, Dr. Jeannette (Box 14)
    - Sullivan, Dr. Arthur L. (Box 14)
- Accession Number A93-19
  - The Origin and First Thirty-Five Years of D.U.M.L. by Cazlyn G. Bookhout (Box 14)
- Accession Number A93-120
  - Provost Correspondence
    - 1979-1983 (Box 14)
    - 1984 (Box 14)
    - 1985 (Box 14)
    - JDC, March 19, 1985 (Box 14)
    - 1986 (Box 14)
    - February 25, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Re: Budget, December 9, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Re: Equip/Facs, December 9, 1986 (Box 15)
    - 1987 (Box 15)
    - February 18, 1987-February 19, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Re: Money/Duties, July 7, 1988 (Box 15)
    - August 24, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1979-1988 (Box 15)
  - Greetings - DUML - 50th, 1988, 1979-1988 (Box 15)
  - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1938- 1988 (Box 15)
  - Duke - Ad/Environmental Studies, 1990 (Box 15)
- Accession UA2018.0075
  - Life at DML, 1980-1990 (Box 16)
    Scope and Contents
    In inventory as: NB1; color slides
  - R/V Cape Hatteras, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB2; color
  - Bonaventura phyle, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB3; color
  - R/V Cape Hatteras, 1981 August-1985 April (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB4; black-and-white negatives and contact sheet
  - Employee slides, 1981 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB5; color slides
  - DUML General Slides, 1981-1989 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB6; color
  - Alumni Weekends, 1982-1986 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB7; color slides
  - Mugs (Passport Photos), 1983 November (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB8; black-and-white negatives and contact sheets
  - Hatteras/Puerto Rico, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB9; color
  - R/V Cape Hatteras- San Juan, REU, 1984 February, 1988 August (Box 16)
    In inventory as: NB10; black-and-white negatives and contact sheets
  - DUML Aerials, 1984-1999 (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB11; black-and-white and color negatives, slides and prints
  - Hatteras Trip of GA, 1985 April (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB12; color
  - DML 50 years, 1988 June (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB13; black-and-white and color
  - General/Historic DML, 1980s-1990s (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB14; color
  - R/V Cape Hatteras, 1980s-1990s (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB15; color
  - R/V Cape Hatteras, 1993 (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB16; color
  - Dolphin Captures, 1995 July 11, 1995 July 17 (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB17; black-and-white and color slides
  - Boat and Island Trips, 1996 September 01 (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB18; color slides
  - DML and LSRC, 1997 January-March (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB19; black-and-white
  - BBSR and Local Bermuda, 1997 April 07-12 (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB20; color
  - DML, Graduation, Field Day, Picnic, Bermuda, 1997 April-May (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB21; black-and-white
  - Field Work, 1997 May-June (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB22; color
  - Faculty, Courses, Trips, 1997 June-August (Box 17)
    In inventory as: NB23; black-and-white
  - DML Courses, 1997 July (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB24; color
  - Life and Field Trips, 1997 September-December (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB25; black-and-white
  - Course Trips, 1997 September-1998 April (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB26; color
  - Graduation, Field Day, Trips, 1998 (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB27; black-and-white
  - Course Trips, 1998 May-August (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB28; black-and-white
  - Summer Courses, 1998 May-September (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB29; color
  - DML Life and Trips, 1998 September-December (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB30; black-and-white
  - Boat and Canoe Trips, 1998 September-1999 April (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB31; color
  - Courses, Boat Trips, Field Day, 1999 January-May (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB32; black-and-white
  - Boat Trips, 1999 May 01 (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB33; color
  - Summer Courses, Coastal Issues Forum, 1999 May-June (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB34; black-and-white
  - Conservation Bio and Turtle Class, 1999 July (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB35; black-and-white
  - Fall Courses and Snow, 1999 September-December (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB36; color
  - Course Trips, 1999 September-2000 March (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB37; black-and-white
  - Bonaventura Slides, circa 1980 (Box 18)
    In inventory as: NB38; color
  - R/V Cape Hatteras Photolog (Box 19)
    color prints
  - Scrapbook of news clippings about DUML, 1960s (Box 19)